howtouncle.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy | How To Uncle

At [How To Uncle](http://www.howtouncle.com/) the privacy of our readers/visitors is exceedingly important. This Privacy Policy outlines the all types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.                                                                                                                                                       

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit [Howtouncle.com](http://www.howtouncle.com/), and how we safeguard your information.

_“We never sell your personal information to third parties”_

**1\. Log Files**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

* IP (Internet Protocol) addresses 

* Your ISP (airtel, bsnl, mtnl, tata etc….)

* Types of browser you used to visit our site

* Date and time stamp

* Referring and exit pages

* Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

**2\. Cookies**

We do use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, How To Uncle has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

 Last Updated: _2 june, 2014_
